<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts - No-BS.xyz</title>
    <link>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on No-BS.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Reasons I&#39;m Leaving (traditional) Social Media</title>
      <link>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/2021/01/07/reasons-im-leaving-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/2021/01/07/reasons-im-leaving-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Polarization: division into two sharply distinct opposites.
Privacy: the state of being free from public attention or unsanctioned intrusion.
Attention: the ability or power to keep the mind on something.
These are the primary reasons I&amp;rsquo;m leaving the more traditional social media sites. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll be making the case for why these traditional sites move us in a direction away from the optimal positions in these three important areas of modern living, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be linking alternative tools below that supplement or replace these original websites more effectively.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>The JuliaLang Paradox</title>
      <link>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/2020/01/29/the-julialang-paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/2020/01/29/the-julialang-paradox/</guid>
      <description>The beginning of this post is going to sound ridiculous, but I promise it is 100% true. One night went to bed trying to remember the name of an interesting programming language that I heard about a while back. It supposedly had a lot of super nifty features, and was some strange hybrid of multiple languages that still somehow worked. I was intrigued, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember, so I decided to just go to sleep and figure it out in the morning.</description>
    </item><item>
      <title>Maximizing Productivity Via The Command Line</title>
      <link>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/2019/12/14/maximizing-productivity-via-the-command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://johnabs.github.io/PA_blog/post/2019/12/14/maximizing-productivity-via-the-command-line/</guid>
      <description>Those who know me know I am a huge fan of GNU/Linux (for you Stallman), and I originally got into it to help me with a few chemistry simulations in my quantum mechanics and statistical dynamics course in undergrad. Specifically, my professor made a huge deal about turning in lab reports that were formatted ever-so precisely, and to kill two birds with one stone, I installed Linux on my computer to help me learn and interface with the supercomputer, and installed LaTeX to help with the lab report issue.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>